[Music]
[Música]
What's up with the kids? Well, let me
qué pasa a la chavalería bueno
remind you that today at 8 we have the
recordaros que hoy tenemos a las 8 el
second day of the Squid Games tournament. Okay,
segundo día del torneo de los juegos del
and if I announce it on the
calamar vale y si os lo anuncio por
street, pass the first day in the morning,
calle pase el primer día de la mañana ya
tomorrow I don't know if I'll be announcing the
mañana no sé si estaré anunciando el
third. I don't think so, but anyway, let me remind you
tercero no lo creo pero bueno recordaros
that at
que a las 8 en mi canal de tweets no
8 on my tweet channel, don't make plans, set your alarm, don't leave me stranded. Okay, I'll probably start earlier, I'll start at about 7:30 by warming up and well, I'll see you there. We had a great time. Ibai, the evening of the year 2 will be held
ibai la velada del año 2 se celebrará
this summer. Whoever wants to
este mismo verano quien quiera
participate, reply to this tweet. It will be
participar que responda a este tuit será
the event of the year, I assure you.
el evento del año os lo aseguro
Well,
bueno
this was expected, it was expected. There will
esto ya se esperaba se esperaba ti va a
be a second edition.
haber una segunda edición la del año
Last year was a success, to be honest, you
pasado fue un éxito a mí sinceramente es
know that sports don't really
que ya sabéis que los deportes no me
catch my attention, for me it's all this
llaman la atención para mí es el tema
tournament stuff, so we
este de los torneos y demás así que los
follow them, not to keep up with the salsa music
seguimos no para seguir el salsero que
and all that, but the truth is that I didn't
hay y demás pero a esto la verdad que no
pay much attention to this last year
le eche mucha cuenta el año pasado
because of the sports and  I've never
porque tema deporte y el boxeo nunca me
liked boxing it never attracts attention
ha gustado nunca más llama la atención
anymore I understand that it entertains you and so on it
nada yo entiendo que os divierta y demás
was very successful I don't remember in terms of
tuvo mucho éxito no me acuerdo en cuanto
audience it probably had between 800
a audiencia tuvo seguramente entre 800
thousand and a million I think it was I don't remember I don't
mil y un millón creo que fue no me
think that much I don't think it
acuerdo no creo que tanto no creo que
was between half a million 800 thousand I don't
fue entre medios millones 800 mil no lo
know how to put it except the
sé poner menos la caja de los
comments box that I don't remember I'm
comentarios que no lo recuerdo ya os
telling you it's that I didn't pay attention the only thing
digo es que no le eche cuenta lo único
I remember was that last year it
que me acuerdo que esto el año pasado no
wasn't summer I think it was before summer
fue verano creo que fue antes de verano
because that was when the mess in
porque fue cuando se lió la de la de
Greece with the positive in Kobe no the
grecia con el positivo en kobe no el
counter tested positive the people there well
contador dio positivo la gente allí
this year luckily things
bueno pues este año la cosa por suerte
seem to be a little better because the
parece que está un poco mejor porque la
people who yes it's true that they are getting
gente que sí que verdad que se está
infected so much whiskey I mean
contagiando tanto whisky o sea a día de
today everyone is getting infected I
hoy se está contagiando todo quisque yo
think that in the end we will all end up going through it
creo que al final acabaremos pasándolo
but not as bad not as bad
todos pero no tan fuerte no tan fuerte
as they are like or at least some for
como están como o al menos algunos por
example some play went through 88 a
ejemplo a unos play lo ha pasado 88 un
month to a job they had a terrible time let's go
mes a un empleo lo ha pasado fatal vamos
by what was
por lo que por lo que nos estaba
guiding us a good mass is who I know  who's
orientando buena masa es quien sé quién
signing up for this no because I'm sure there
se apunta esto no porque esto seguro que
are a ton of people here in the
hay un montón de gente aquí en la
answer already signing up some will be
respuesta ya apuntándose algunos serán
from last year and others were new not even
los del año pasado y otros eran nuevo ni
sachs nice Chernoff suit for god's sake I wouldn't
sachs terno niza chernoff por dios no me
like them to do anything to you not even third
gustaría que te hicieran nada ni tercer
shift okay don't show up you give trust in
turno vale no te presentes das confía en
my fists I put on a
mis puños me pongo una careta de
christine mask and plug it in favor has
christine y le enchufa a favor
previously had only one
ha tenido anterior un solo canal de
youtube channel parked to become a
youtube aparcado para convertirme en una
killing machine this is my moment
máquina de matar es mi momento
efe
efe
congratulations this is how it will remain whoever
felicito así va a quedar el que se
dares against me can add
atreva contra mí puede adicionar
christina and say I want to go see this
christina y dice yo quiero ir a ver esto
while I enjoy a drink for
mientras disfruto de un copazo por
carola if next year it happens again you
carola si el año que viene se repite se
can request to get in the ring I'm going to
puede solicitar subirse al ring lo voy a
try save tweets okay
intentar guarden tweets valen
quiet challenging dario m
quieto retando a darío m
dario m milk I think that I would not
darío m leche yo creo que yo no lo
challenge him dario de leche I mean one thing is
retaría dario de leche o sea una cosa es
criticizable but another thing a
criticable pero otra cosa un combate de
boxing match a boxing match this this one hits
boxeo un combate de boxeo este este pega
hard I mean leasing issues
fuerte o sea temas de leasing sin
toothless no and attentive because I don't know what to
dientes no y atento pues no sé yo qué
tell you if he is so  enable as
decirte si está tan habilitar así como
with Dario but well he's cool challenging
con el darío pero bueno está cheto
Dario it would be the presence of the
retando a darío sería la presencia del
internet or there where he says ar and what does
internet o allí en el que dice ar y que
ari say but now really stay in
dice ari pero ahora de verdad quédate en
Latin America for a few months my sister what a
latinoamérica unos meses mi hermana que
mess if you've already traveled here if you
vaya tela si has viajado ya para acá si
come here every moment you're going to have
es que vienes a cada momento te vas a
the active purchase a second
tener el compra aqtiva una segunda
home he wants to start fighting he doesn't know
vivienda quiere agarrarse a golpes no
who I would put one with I would
pone con quien yo le pondría uno yo le
put a few candidates for the
pondría unas cuantas candidatas al
job candidate I don't
empleo candidato
know if I don't know if it will be possible in the
no sé si no sé si se podrá en la
category to put men and women in the
categoría poner hombres y mujeres en el
same fight depending on the weight and so on I do
mismo combate dependiendo del peso y
n't know or if it has to be by
demás no lo sé o si tiene que ser por
men men and women against many I don't
hombres hombres y mujeres contra muchos
know I don't know how this is organized
no lo sé no sé cómo se organiza esto
but I would put several candidates and I
pero yo le pondría varias candidatas y
know that you guys would also put it in the
sé que ustedes también ponerlo en la
box like
caja de como
percy is says manguel you for me a lot
percy está dice manguel tú para mí mucha
and a lot of money
y mucha pasta
you for me and a lot of money I think it's a I
tú para mí y mucha pasta
think it's a challenge or the
creo que es una creo que es un reto o el
morera boy the morera boy
chico morera el chico morera
I didn't get into the ring with the mont boy it
yo no me subí al ring con el chico mont
was the moreras boy he has
era el chico moreras ha
changed a lot physically in
cambiado mucho físicamente en los
recent years and he has two arms that are
últimos años y tiene dos brazos que son
two  hams but of these fingers that are
dos jamones pero de estos dedos que
worth three hundred to you you know those with
valen trescientos para vos sabes de los
hard hams they know about
de los jamones duros saben de los amores
powerful loves and here I myself say that see what
potentes y aquí dice yo misma que ve lo
this has been forging for years Dallas
que esto lleva años forjándose dallas
well Dallas would
pues dallas
not be accepted
no se aceptaría
well Dallas I don't know if he would accept with the
pues dallas no sé si aceptaría con el
Morel boy the truth is that on
chico morel a la verdad que da las
many occasions he has said of challenging
muchas ocasiones ha dicho de retar a
people to share legal devotion and the
gente a compartir devoción legales y la
truth is that it would be wonderful will remain
verdad que sería maravilloso quedará
participate in some of this with someone with
participará en algo de esto con alguno
some with some who have
con algunos con algunos que le haya
really touched his nose okay in boys
tocado bien las narices vale en chicos
ways he touched his nose in his day
maneras le tocó las narices en su día
but not in a super way sometimes I
pero tampoco en plan súper a veces yo
understand that it continues that it does not stay at the
entiendo que sigue que no se queda al
level that I do not know for the you will be able to level
nivel que no sé por la podrás nivel a
today yet but whatever it is a
día de hoy todavía pero lo que sea es
thing of the past no longer I would rather
cosa del pasado ya no yo más bien a
put Dallas with other people also I
dallas lo pondría con otra gente también
also leave it that will emerge it is in the
también lo dejo que surgirá es en la
comments box
caja de comentarios
but still it would still be powerful
pero todavía todavía estaría potente
I want to fight with someone he says he has
yo quiero pegarme con alguien dice lleva
a hair
un pelo
zhang I do not know him what else do you
zhang no lo conozco que más te hace
need and he is going to go comment
falta y va a ir comentar
that he hit me bro
que que me pegó hermano
but because I love
pero porque me encanta
the experience of being  there hitting with
la experiencia de estar allí pegando con
attention the adrenaline
la atención la adrenalina
everyone looking at you the subject that
todo el mundo mirándote el tema de que
I love contact sports
me encantan los deportes de contacto
because I love boxing I
porque a mí me encanta el boxeo me
love it like a presentation video
encanta el como un vídeo de presentación
that has been made not even a video video
que se ha hecho no sea un vídeo vídeo
resume has not been made this man I don't
currículum no se ha hecho este hombre no
know who they have let's see he has his has
sé quiénes han a ver tiene tiene su
his followers of Joselito and in
tiene sus seguidores de joselito y en
Marbella you go to well from Malaga look at the
marbella vais a pues de málaga mira el
neighbor and
vecino
you if I can go plug me in you follow me
y tú yo si puedo ir enchufa me seguís
snoring watching it quietly it's like
ronco la viéndolo tranquilito es como
this is one of mine it's to me if it is like that if you
este es de los míos es a mí si es así si
can request that they invite you like that
se puede solicitar que te inviten así a
me so they can also invite my
mí así también me pueden invitar a mis
friends and they can also invite me it's your
amigas y también me pueden invitar a te
turn you get used to it piss yourself off I saw
toca te habitúes tocarte los huevos vi
you see what face he has bastard sol more I
tu ver qué cara tiene cabrón sol más me
would love to participate and Bentez magic
encantaría participar y benítez mágina
how many they are man against all
cuánto son man contra todos
this gel to the spur I have
este gel al espolón
not done boxing in my life but if I
no he hecho boxeo en mi vida pero si
had the opportunity I would give my best and I
tuviera la oportunidad daría el máximo y
would train every day the hours that
entrenaría todos los días las horas que
were necessary to be at the top
fueran necesarias para estar a la altura
dedication I would not lack I mean guys don't
dedicación no me faltaría o sea tíos no
have time because you have to  use it
tiene tiempo porque tienes que emplearlo
in your company in your work and all the
en tu empresa en tu trabajo y todo el
stuff that you were not going to be marijuana but they
rollo que no ibais a ser marihuana pero
would train the hours that it takes to be
entrenarían las horas que sea por estar
in combat the end ec and ready dude that
en el combate el fin ec y listo tío
study do not see the brands how they
que ese estudio no vean las marcas como
eat his ass and dance since very well
le comen el culo y baile ya que muy bien
for the value of his balls because for
por el valor de sus huevos porque para
the wonderful but sometimes it
el maravilloso lo pero algunas veces se
looks a little regrettable there is no country there are
ve un poco lamentable no hay país hay
places where they do not hit no and tweets that do
lugares donde no pegan no y tweets que
not hit no but but this bread is for
no pegan no pero pero este pan este para
menotti or so that people
menotti o para que para que la gente
say or I [ __ ] love the one from covirn or I [ __ ] love
diga o [__] amo el de covirán o [__] amo
the one from telefono or I [ __ ] love the one from the
el de telefónica o [__] amo el de la
croquette store on the corner hahaha
tienda de croquetas de la esquina jajaja
because people the kids many
porque la gente los chavales muchas
times that nonsense is very funny they
veces esas tonterías les hace muchas
follow companies because they
gracias siguen a las empresas porque lo
find it funny because of the meme that it should
ven divertido por el meme de que tendría
be that they should tweet
que ser de que tendrían que twittear
things series and twitter in these things well
cosas series y twitter en estas cosas
sometimes I violate them mentally
pues yo algunas veces las viola mental
right magnetized that he is with us in
verdad imantado que está con nosotros en
the tournament and I go and I go with everything looking for my
el torneo y va y voy con todo busca mi
rival who swelled him with his fist Marc and madness
rival que le hinchó a puño marc y locura
I want to go see him this fact is capable
yo quiero ir a verlo este hecho es capaz
of starting to break the stands of starting
de ponerse a partir la grada de ponerse
to hit chairs or something like that, so
a pegar sillas o por ahí sabe así que sí
yes, it's better if they invite him but in the
sí esté mejor que lo inviten pero en la
stands it's worth it in the
grada vale
back and I don't know if he'll stream this
atrás y no sé si stream en este
quarter too
trimestre también
and also because of the physical fight that
y también debido a la pelea física que
the streamers are going to have, guys, last night
van a tener los streamer chavales anoche
on streaming I made a table of what would
en streaming hice una tabla de qué
happen if I stayed with the
pasaría si yo me quedase con la
electric girl, what do you think? Well, I have
eléctrica chavala que os parece
no idea because I don't understand
pues que ni idea porque no entiendo de
anything but well, you're the one I want to be the one
nada pero bueno a sos el yo quiero ser
behind supporting those who
el que esté detrás apoyando a los que se
fight if here there are many like me here, there are
peleen si aquí hay mucho como yo he aquí
many like me from you or the list so that they
mucho como yo de ti o la lista para que
beat me up with blows from you, countrywoman, a
me revienten a hostias de ti paisana un
huge kiss
beso enorme
Luz, date I'll be there Luces that
luz fecha que estaré allí luces que el
last year the baby was still very small, I
año pasado tenía el bebé muy pequeño
think that's why he didn't come, I
todavía creo por eso no vino
think it was because of that
creo que fue por eso
Bauer who is Coll and Guitart Banesco you
bauer que es coll y guitart banesco le
take ours off the channel you are very good
quitas nuestros del canal eres muy buena
people me against Dembl
gente yo contra dembélé
and well well well well well he
y bueno bueno bueno bueno bueno
is a tweeter that I always see him I see him a
es un tuitero que siempre lo veo lo veo
lot everywhere I have no idea
mucho por todos lados no tengo ni idea
who and what he does, let's see, I do
de quién y de qué es lo que hace a ver
n't know if YouTube I don't know  if they write I don't know
no sé si youtube no sé si escriben no sé
what he does but I always see it
qué es lo que hace pero siempre lo veo
all over the place
por todos
libra de he lowered me to whoever I
libra de me bajó a quien sea
want to hit me with blows I don't care who
yo quiero pegarme de hostias me da igual
puts me in front Jordi Machiavelli
que me ponga delante jordi maquiavelo
Lolita I already said everything without fear of
lolita yo ya lo dije todo sin miedo a
dying so they say also
morir tan dicen también
this one if I'm not mistaken he's the editor of
este si no me equivoco es el editor de
ibai the editor of ibai himself a royal
ibai el propio editor de ibai un royal
rumble
rumble
and Andorrans whoever wins stays in
y andorranos el que gane se queda en
Andorra the rest have to return and
andorra los demás tienen que volver y
pay taxes we all win
pagar impuestos a todos salimos ganando
this way surely paying more taxes
así seguramente pagando más impuestos
surely we win everything and well the
seguro que ganamos todo y bueno los
others good or Susana me to hit me no
demás buenos o susana yo para pegarme no
but to watch it from the stands with a
pero para verlo desde la grada con una
beer I'm seeing and the thing is that here
cervecita estoy ver y es que es que aquí
here the vast majority are like me
hay aquí la gran mayoría son como yo es
and I invite even if it's to put Cuba
y yo invita aunque sea para poner cuba
is here the vast majority are are from
está aquí la gran mayoría son son de los
mine no maybe a rematch I laid a base
míos no quizás una revancha eché base
now the million for sure sure sure sure that he will
ahora el millón seguro seguro segurísimo
show up again that
segurísimo que se presenta otra vez que
and that as he says surely I
y que como bien dice él seguramente
tried a rematch he will have the same
intenté una revancha tendrá el mismo
says
dice
God it's January but I think I can
dios estamos a enero pero creo que puedo
temper my body so that my back doesn't hurt
templar mi cuerpo para que no me duela
yes  my
la espalda si me pega
little body suits me, it also has damage, it's a
el cuerpecito también tiene daño es un
little bit out of shape, he's a little bit
poco tampoco en forma está un poco
active and like me, but I think it's
actividades y como yo pero yo creo que
worse, it's that he's less in
queda yo está peor es que está menos en
shape, go from him, if I can go with my
forma vaya de él yo si puedo ir con mi
representative by stacks, I'm in, yes, I
representante by stacks me apunto eso sí
'm old, don't go too far,
ya estoy mayor no te pases
this is a feminist of this that I know goes all
esta es una feminista de esta que se que
out with the vibes and joins in on
se mete a saco con onda las y se une a
all the cancellations of all the people,
todas las cancelaciones de toda la gente
so in the threads and such, I don't want to
así que en los hilos y demás no quiero
participate, create a female category
participar crear una categoría femenina
please, let's see, create a female category
porfa a ver crear una categoría femenina
would be discriminatory, valuable to me, it wouldn't have to do
sería discriminar valiosa para mí no
with gender, it would have to
tendría que ver con el género tendría
do with weight, don't correct me if I'm
que ver con el peso no corregirme si me
wrong in the comments box, because
equivoco en la caja de comentarios que a
maybe since I'm illiterate in
lo mejor que yo como soy un analfabeto
sports, I'm wrong, but it
los deportes me estoy equivocando pero
shouldn't or shouldn't depend on weight,
no debe o no debería depender del peso
weight and height more than weight, height
peso y estatura más que de peso estatura
difference, maybe more than gender. I
diferencia a lo mejor más que del género
ask, it is asked, a coral, coral measures
pregunto es preguntó un coral coral mide
with a key, I fight with courage, it's not the
con llave peleo con coraje tampoco es el
coral, tam, my beloved,
coral tam amadísimo
but the same, she would show her face in
pero mismo mismo daría la cara en
person, she hasn't done a face devil
persona ella no ha hecho un face devil
tobiano
tobiano
reveal face real fitur fitur
revel face real
feature, she will surely participate
fitur fitur feature seguro que participa
in  what's
a través
done is done and now more secure
lo hecho hecho está y ahora más seguro
now here in the answer we
ahora aquí en la respuesta nos
meet yes or yes you want to make a
encontramos si o si quieres hacerte una
promo for the pay and that's it but nothing
promo por la pagas y ya está pero nada
more that [ __ ]
más esa [__]
woman Mariana let's
mujer mariana
see the sea is not very tall anymore uncle
a ver el mar ya no es muy alto de tío
measures two meters the width is thin
mide dos metros el ancho está delgado
is thin let's see us work weight
está delgado a vernos trabajo de peso
but he celebrates because of course it's
pero él celebra porque claro es más
longer a day without bread I
largo un día sin pan
already think that people like that known are running out
ya creo que se van acabando la gente así
ay babies'r'us is very bad also
ay babies'r'us está malísimo también
there's a kid from this koi team
ahí hay un chaval del equipo este de koi
but he doesn't have
pero no se tiene
manute the kid that we were there
manute el chaval que estuvimos allí
hiding in the game of hide and seek
escondiendo en el juego del escondite
[Music]
[Música]
well family what do you think
pues familiar qué pensáis ustedes al que
we would like to see there the truth is
nos gustaría ver por ahí a mí la verdad
that I would like to see a lot more people than
que me gustaría ver a mucha más gente de
what came last year I already tell you or
la que fue el año pasado yo ya te digo o
I mean to one thing this I wouldn't show up not
sea yo a una cosa esta no me presentaba
even crazy I took I would go to like those
ni loco yo me tomé yo me iría a como los
who are saying oh my friend habits
que están diciendo ay mi colega hábitos
and some more not like to see him
y algunos más no en plan a toa a verlo
with a beer and for a pack of
con una cervecita y por un paquete de
seeds you know
pipas sabes
and little else you know why because I value
y poco más sabes por qué porque valoro
my teeth I value my face  and the truth is
mis dientes valoro mi cara y la verdad
that I'm willing to lose it there will
que estoy dispuesto a perderlo
surely be someone also
seguramente habrá alguien también
asking for the ones mentioned
pidiendo los los citados
let's take a look let's take a look
echemos un vistazo echemos un vistazo
but what are giving a lot of people would be a
pero que está dando mucha gente sería un
little look at my chick says I
poco mira a mi pollito dice vi cercado
saw fenced wake up and train mind we have a pool ism that expands the boxing base chick I want them to hurt you for real I'm telling you well what do you think family always be reading with respect to everyone please propose what fights you would like to see in this in this seventeenth edition and in look minimum and the fifteenth and download it
xvii y en mira mínimo y el xv y bajarlo
to the brother the brother is
al hermano al hermano está retando
always challenging with respect to the family
siempre con respecto al familiar
respect all the people I
respetar a todas las personas de las que
'm talking about but here with twitter
estoy hablando pero aquí con el twitter
my dear field and nothing familiar
mi querido campo y nada familiar nos
see you in the next video don't leave me
vemos en el siguiente vídeo no me dejéis
pulled today please don't leave me pulled
tira hoy por favores no me deje tirado
because today I need a lot of
que que hoy necesito mucha energía
positive energy okay a hug
positiva vale un abrazo
no
no
[Music]
[Música]